asbhawaii.com 2004-12-10

# ASB Hawaii - Privacy Policy

**CORPORATE PRIVACY POLICY**

At American Savings Bank ("American Savings"), protecting the privacy and confidentiality of your Personal Information is important. We value your business and the trust you have placed in American Savings to provide a safe and secure environment for personally identifiable information about you and your finances, which we will call in this Privacy Policy your "Personal Information." It is our policy that all Personal Information about you will be held in strictest confidence. American Savings does not sell or share your Personal Information or Personal Information about our former customers to non-affiliated third parties outside the American Savings family of companies except for those companies who work for us and as permitted by law. To help you better understand how we protect your Personal Information, we are providing you with the following Privacy Policy describing our privacy practices and policies with respect to your Personal Information pursuant to the Federal Financial Privacy Law. 

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We collect, maintain, and use information about you on a routine basis in order to offer you the financial services and products you seek to obtain and to provide superior customer service. We use all of your Personal Information we collect for specific business purposes such as administering and servicing your accounts, complying with state/federal banking regulations, protecting against fraud, and developing a better understanding of your financial needs to provide you with improved products and services. Personal Information we collect falls within the following five categories: 

  1. Personal Information provided by you during the application process for a deposit, loan, brokerage account, and/or insurance policy, other forms, or interviews with our employees when opening an account with us, such as your name, address, Social Security number, investments, assets and income;   

  2. Personal Information gathered from your transactions and experiences with us and our affiliates, such as account balances, payment history, securities and insurance products purchased and credit usage;   

  3. Personal Information obtained from your transactions and experiences with other parties, such as your account balances, payment history, parties to the transaction and credit card usage;  

  4. Personal Information obtained from other authorized sources, such as consumer credit reporting agencies; and  

  5. Personal information we obtain from third-parties about you and your employment, credit, health and medical information or other relationships with them, such as your employment and health and medical history and credit balances which we use for various purposes, such as verifying your statements to us.  

**SHARING PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES  
**   
We do not disclose your Personal Information or any Personal Information about our current or former customers to any affiliate or nonaffiliated third party except as permitted by law. We may disclose all of your Personal Information described above with third parties for the purpose of servicing your loan and deposit accounts with us and insurance and investment products purchased through us, such as printing your checks, mailing your account statements, running credit or check verifications, servicing a brokerage account, processing an insurance claim, processing transactions that you have requested or authorized.

We may share your Personal Information with third parties who conduct marketing services on our behalf and other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. Those third parties are contractually obligated to keep your Personal Information provided to them confidential, and to use the information only to provide the service we have asked them to perform. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURITY  
  **  
We restrict access to your Personal Information to those employees who need to know the Personal Information to provide our products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to protect your Personal Information.

**SHARING PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OUR AFFILIATES**

  American Savings may share all five of the categories of your Personal Information described above with our affiliates. For example, we may disclose all five categories of your Personal Information to our affiliate Bishop Insurance Agency of Hawaii, Inc. which sells a variety of insurance products. We also may share all five categories of your Personal Information to our non-financial company affiliate, AdCommunications, who assists us with the advertising and marketing of our products and services. We work with our affiliates to provide the products and services you want and need. By sharing your Personal Information with our affiliates, American Savings is able to offer its customers insurance products.

**LIMITING OUR SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

  If you do not want us to share your Personal Information obtained from your applications, consumer reports or from other outside sources with our affiliates, please tell us of this request by calling 627-6900 (toll free 1-800-272-2566) or dropping off the opt-out form at any American Savings branch. **If you previously opted out and wish to continue your opt out, you do not need to do anything.** If you are a joint accountholder, we will treat your request for us not to share that Personal Information with our affiliates as applying only to you and not to other joint accountholders, unless you inform us that your instruction applies to all of the joint accountholders, or all of the other joint accountholders individually or jointly request us not to share that Personal Information with our affiliates. Please note that it may take two to four weeks to make your request fully effective and you will still be contacted as necessary to service your accounts or receive marketing information on existing or new American Savings products and services.

If you don't have the Adobe Acrobat Reader, you can get it here:[](http://www.adobe.com/products/acrobat/readstep.html)[  
](http://www.adobe.com/products/acrobat/readstep.html)

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We will provide you with our Privacy Policy annually, so long as you maintain an on-going customer relationship with us. 

If you have any questions that are not answered in this section please contact us.
